<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Let&#39;s Learn: Playwright on Learn Playwright</title>
    <link>https://nitya.github.io/learn-playwright/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Let&#39;s Learn: Playwright on Learn Playwright</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nitya.github.io/learn-playwright/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>#001 - Getting Started (Part 1)</title>
      <link>https://nitya.github.io/learn-playwright/001-getting-started-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 16:21:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nitya.github.io/learn-playwright/001-getting-started-setup/</guid>
      <description>Getting Started - Part 1  Welcome to Day 1 of #30DaysOfPlaywright!!
 Today&amp;rsquo;s goal is to make progress on the Getting Started tutorial which should get us set up with the Playwright Test runner in our local development environment - and get us configured to do our first test run.
There&amp;rsquo;s a lot covered in there, so I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to break this into multiple parts.
  Part 1: - Install the Playwright Test runner and validate setup by completing your first test run with the sample test script.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello, #30DaysOfPlaywright</title>
      <link>https://nitya.github.io/learn-playwright/000-hello-30days/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 10:22:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nitya.github.io/learn-playwright/000-hello-30days/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;rsquo;s Learn About Testing! It&amp;rsquo;s December 1! The new year is just over 30 days away so it&amp;rsquo;s the perfect time to make a learning resolution, get started on it now - and then check it off the very first day of the New Year! So what do you want to learn this year?
I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to invest this month exploring a topic that fascinates me - end-to-end testing for modern web apps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About This Project</title>
      <link>https://nitya.github.io/learn-playwright/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 10:38:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nitya.github.io/learn-playwright/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello - I&amp;rsquo;m Nitya! 👋🏽
This blog documents my learning journey into all things related to cross-browser testing, test automation and end-to-end testing for web and multi-platform apps using the Playwright framework and tooling ecosystem.
I&amp;rsquo;m kicking things off in Dec 2021 with a #30DaysOfPlaywright content series where I&amp;rsquo;ll everything from core testing concepts, to Playwright tools, APIs &amp;amp; best practices for end-to-end testing of modern web applications.
Join me!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
